YALING ZHANG

A Nursing Student with entry-level experience providing direct patient care as a certified nursing assistant and nurse extern. Achieved recognition from physicians and RNs during clinical evaluations for delivering patient-centered care and communicating with empathy and compassion.

123 Bridge Street, Boston, MA 12345 ya I i ngzhang@exam p le.com (123) 456-7890 LinkedIn I Portfolio

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

NURSING EXTERN

Ardmore Hospital, Boston, MA May 2023-July 2023

- Provided direct care to an average of five patients per shift under the supervision of the charge nurse and clinical preceptor
- ◆ Administered medications using the oral, topical, and subcutaneous routes
- Performed patient assessments and coordinated with registered nurses to develop comprehensive care plans based on symptoms and individual needs
- Monitored patients following surgical procedures, provided wound care, changed dressings, and updated the nurse manager on changes in patient condition

CERTIFIED NURSING ASSISTANT

Kindred Medical Center, Boston, MA October 2021- May 2023

- Deliver patient care under the supervision of RNs and LPNs, assist patients with ADLs, and collaborate with nursing teams to enhance the patient experience, resulting in a 15% increase in patient satisfaction scores
- Measure and record patient vital signs in electronic medical record system and provide updates to resident nurses on changes in patient medical status and symptoms

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) Nursing Boston College, Boston, MA September 2019 - May 2023

KEY SKILLS

- ◆ Patient-Centered Care
- ♦ Communication
- ♦ Wound Care
- Clinical Operations
- Acute Care

CERTIFICATIONS

- Regi ste red N u rse, State of Massachusetts, License #123456
- Certifi ed N u rs i ng Assi sta n t, Sta te of Massachusetts, License #123456
- Basic Life Support Certifications,
 American Heart Association, 2023